Guide to the Mann Library records, 1908-2011.
Mann Library records, 1908-2011
- Series IV. Budget
  - Book Fund Division-Expenditures, 1914-1917 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Department Balances, 1914-1915 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Funds spent in June, 1916 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Book Orders, 1914-1915 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Book Orders, 1915-1916 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Orders, Bills, Memoranda, 1915-1916 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Reimbursement-Traveling expenses, 1915 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Subscription information, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Subscriptions-Paid Direct, 1916 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Appropriations-Animal Husbandry, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Appropriations-Botany, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Appropriations-Chemistry, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Appropriations-Dairy, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Appropriations-Drawing, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - Appropriations-Education-Rural, 1917 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Appropriations-Entomology, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Appropriations-Extension, 1917 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Appropriations-Farm Crops, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Appropriations-Farm Management, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - Appropriations-Forestry, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - Appropriations-Home Economics, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - Appropriations-Horticulture, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 54)
  - Appropriations-Landscape Art, 1917 (Box 36, Folder 55)
  - Appropriations-Plant Breeding, 1917 (Box 36, Folder 56)
  - Appropriations-Plant Pathology, 1917 (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - Appropriations-Pomology, 1917 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Appropriations-Poultry, 1917 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Appropriations-Rural Economy, 1917 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Appropriations-Rural Engineering, 1917 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Appropriations-Soils, 1917 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Appropriations-Vegetable Gardening, 1917 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Paid Invoices, 1917-1918 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Paid Invoices, 1918-1919 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Paid Invoices, 1919 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Paid Invoices, 1919-1920 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Paid Invoices, 1920 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Unpaid Invoices, 1919 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Library Budget Requests (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Prices and Price Indexes, 1961-1981 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Statements-Mann Library Expenditures, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Revenue, 1987-07-1987-12 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Income, 1987-07-1988-06 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Statements-Account Balance, 1986-07-1987-06 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Mann Library Expenditures, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Account Balances, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Financial Statements-Mann Library Expenditures, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Account Balances, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Account Balances, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Account Balances, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Account Balances, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Account Balances, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Account Balances, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Account Balances, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - SUNY Library Data, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Budget Allocations, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Budget Prep for Conference (March 19, 1981), 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Budget Hearing Material, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Budget Request, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - SMIS-Phase I (Statutory Management Information System), 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - SUNY Library Data, Fall 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Budget Allocations, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Budget Materials-Phase I, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Statutory Units-Statutory Financial Planning Process, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Budget Hearing, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - State Budget Deliberations, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Budget Hearing Material, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Dean's Equipment, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - SUNY Library Data, Fall 1983 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Budget Allocations, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Budget Materials, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Phase I- Human Ec and ALS Statutory Financial Planning Process, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Budget Meeting, 1984-03-19 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Mann Library Program Conference, 1984-03-21 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Departmental Planning Conference, 1983-1984, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Budget Conference Material, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - SUNY Library Data, Fall 1984 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Budget Allocations, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Planning Documents, Part I, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Planning Documents, Part II, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - CALS Private Support, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Mann Library-Microcomputer Center Student Employment Report, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Library Allocation Budget Figures, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Monthly Statistics, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Equipment to Order, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Statutory College Financial Data, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Capital Budget File, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - State Allocations, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Acquisition Expenditures, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Interlibrary Loan Expenditures, 1980-1984 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Temporary Worker- Wages, 1982-1986 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - SUNY Budget Request, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Mann Library Program Conference Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Mann Library Budget Planning, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Mann Library Budget Planning, Cycle I, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Mann Library Budget Planning, Cycle II, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Mann Library Budget Proposed Expenditures, Phase I- Results, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Budget Material, 1918-1961 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Budget-Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Budget Preparation-Mann Library, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Budget Data-SUNY, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Phase I Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Budget Data-SUNY, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Budget Preparation-Mann Library, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Phase I Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Budget Data-SUNY, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Budget Request-Mann Library, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Phase I Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Budget Request, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Phase I Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Budget Data-SUNY, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Budget Request-Mann Library, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Phase I Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Budget Planning, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Budget Request (including some data on 1975-1976), 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Phase I Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Budget Data-SUNY, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Budget Request-Mann Library, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Phase I Budget- ALS & H.Ec., 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Budget Data-SUNY, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Budget Request-Mann Library, 1978- 1979 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Phase I Budget- ALS & H.Ec., 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Budget Hearing, 1979-01 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Budget Data-SUNY, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Budget Request-Mann Library, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Phase I Budget-ALS & H.Ec., 1979- 1980 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Budget Data-SUNY, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Budget Hearing Material, 1980-04-30 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Phase I Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Series V. Meeting Minutes, Reports, and Statistics
  - Library Committee Meeting Minutes, 1908-1911 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Library Committee Meeting Minutes, 1910-1911 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Library Committee Meeting Minutes, 1911-1912 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Library Committee Meeting Minutes, 1912-1913 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Library Committee Meeting Minutes, 1913-1914 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Library Committee Meeting Minutes, 1914-1915 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - EDUCOM Reports, 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - EDUCOM Reports, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Univ. of Philippines, College of Agriculture Library Report- Architectural Floor Plan, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - New York State Library, 1949-1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Middle States Association (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Notis Reports, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Notis Reports, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Academic Assembly Minutes, 1971-1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Academic Assembly Minutes, 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Book Count/Serials Review, 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Cost - Appraisals, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - C.U. Libraries- Director's Reports, 1970-1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - C.U. Libraries- Director's Reports, 1978-1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - C.U. Libraries- Director's Reports, 1942-1951 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - C.U. Libraries- Director's Reports, 1951-1962 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - C.U. Libraries- Director's Reports, 1962-1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Mann Library Annual Reports (to CALS), 1948-1952 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mann Library Annual Reports (to CALS), 1952-1969(1962, 1963 missing) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Glyn Evans- Correspondence, Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Glyn Evans- Correspondence, Reports, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Library Supporting Data, Fall 1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Library Supporting Data, Fall 1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Library Supporting Data, Fall 1982 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - SUNY Library Data, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - SUNY Library Data, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - SUNY Library Data, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - SUNY Library Data, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - SUNY Library Data, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - SUNY Library Data, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - SUNY Library Data, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - SUNY Library Data, 1975-1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - SUNY Library Statistics-Statistical Releases, Memos, Analyses of Trends, 1986-1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - SUNY Library Statistics-Survey Trends, Survey Results (Fall 1989), 1981-1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - SUNY Library Statistics-Library Supporting Data (Fall 1986), Library Service Trends- ILL, 1978-1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - SUNY Library Statistics-Library Supporting Data (Fall 1987), Library Service Trends- ILL, 1978-1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - SUNY Library Statistics-Library Supporting Data (Fall 1988), Library Service Trends- ILL, 1978-1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - SUNY Library Statistics-Library Service Trends, Various Units- ILL, 1978-1988 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - SUNY Library Data, Fall 1986 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - SUNY Library Statistics-Annual Library Reports, 1953-1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - SUNY Library Statistics Report- "Measuring the Use of Library Materials and Services..." by Robert E. Burton, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - SUNY-Biennial Library Reports, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - SUNY Academic Library Statistics, 1967-1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - SUNY Academic Library Statistics, 1979-1983 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - RLG/RLIN, RLG-Aspen, RLIN-linked, Local Systems, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - RLG/RLIN, RLG-Aspen, RLIN-linked, Local Systems, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - RLG/RLIN, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - RLG/RLIN, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Regional History and University Archives [Restricted?] (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - SCRLC Reports, 1968-1975 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - SCLRC Reports, 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Staff Surveys, 1973, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - State Audit, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - State Education Department Report, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Telefax Machine-Correspondence, "Final Report of the National Agricultural Library Telefacsimile Evaluation Report", 1986 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - ACRL /ALA- Minutes, Procedures & Policies, Reports, 1967-1982 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Copyrights- Articles, Correspondence, Reports, 1947- 1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Cranch Report-Correspondence, Memos, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - CONSER (Conservation of Serials) Project Reports- Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Cornell-President/Provost Directives, Reports, Corresondence, Memos, 1951-1985 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Committee on Mission- Report, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Geneva Experiment Station-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, Data, 1953-1964 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Geneva Experiment Station-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, Data, 1965-1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Geneva Experiment Station-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, Data, 1976-1983 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Information- Mann Library, Memos, Brochures, 1953-1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - IAALD (International Assoc. of Agricultural Libraries and Documentalists)-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1956-1980 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Institute for African Development-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1987-1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Institute for African Development-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1987-1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Mann Library Adminstrative Council-Meeting Minutes, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Mann Library Adminstrative Council-Meeting Minutes, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Mann Library Adminstrative Council-Meeting Minutes, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Mann Library Adminstrative Council-Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Mann Library Adminstrative Council-Meeting Minutes, 1984,1985 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - NOTIS (Integrated Library Information System)-Memos, Reports, 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - NOTIS (Integrated Library Information System)-Memos, Reports, 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - NOTIS (Integrated Library Information System)-Memos, Reports, 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - CALS-Integrated Information System, I, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - CALS-Integrated Information System II, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - CALS-"SCET"-Special Committee on Electronic Technology (Correspondence and Reports), 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - CALS-SCET (Correspondence and Reports), 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - CALS-SCET (Correspondence and Reports), 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - CALS Committees-Policy, Curriculum, 1983-1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - CALS Strategic Plan, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - IAALD (International Association of Agricultural Librarians and Documentalists) Executive Committee (Correspondence, Memoranda, Reports), 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - IAALD Executive Committee (Correspondence, Memoranda, Reports), 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - IAALD Executive Committee Meeting, September 13, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Life Safety Reports, 1980-1988 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Mann Library Annual Reports to CALS, 1984-1995 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Acquisitions-Statistics, Reports, Correspondence, Memoranda, 1970-1981 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Acquisitions-Statistics, Reports, Correspondence, Memoranda, 1970-1981 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Artificial Intelligence in Agricultural Research, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Biotechnology Funding, 1983-1989 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Biotechnology Institute, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Biotechnology Transfer Project, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Cataloguing-Memos, Reports, 1953-1959 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cataloguing-Memos, Reports, 1962-1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Chinese Materials-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1979-1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - CUL Annual Report of University Librarian, 1962-1963;1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - CUL Annual Statistics, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - CUL Annual Statistics, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - CUL Annual Statistics, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - CUL Annual Statistics, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - CUL Council of Unit Librarians- Minutes, 1984-1993 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - CUL Digital Library Study Committe, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Departmental Libraries-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1911-1948 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Departmental Libraries-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1948-1958 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - EDUCOM-Correspondence, Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Enviornment Statistics, 1956-1968 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Enrollment Statistics-"Reports, Memos,", 1968-1980 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - International Assoc. of Agricultural Librarians and Documentalists (IAALD)-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1984-1987 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - IAALD Regional Conference-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - IAALD-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - IAALD-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Inter-American Institute for Cooperation on Agriculture (IICA)-Annual Report, Publications, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Mann Library Annual Statistical Reports, 1965- 1974 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Mann Library Annual Statistical Reports, 1974-1980 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Mann Library Annual Statistical Reports, 1980-1984 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Mann Library Organization Chart, 1968-1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - National Agricultural Library-Memos, Reports, 1969-1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - National Agricultural Library-Memos, Reports, 1969-1987 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - New York State Clerical Conference, 1983-1987 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - NYS Education and Research Network (NYSERNet)-Memos, Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - NYSERNet-Memos, Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - NYSERNet-Memos, Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Online Computer Library Center (OCLC)-Memos, Reports, 1974-1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - OCLC-Memos, Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - OCLC-Memos, Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Organization-Memos, Reports, circa 1945-1958 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Organization- Memos, Reports, circa 1945-1958 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Organization-Memos, Reports, circa 1945-1958 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Orientation, Early to 1984 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - PADCT-Letterhead, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Plant Pathology Library and Development (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Portraits, 1958-1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Retrospective Conversion Project- Correspondence, Memos, Reports (ARL) (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - RLG Carnegie Study on Distributive Processing, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - RLG Retrospective Conversion Project, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Student Computing Competencies Committee, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - SUNY Libraries Association Reports, 1979- 1989 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - SUNY Libraries Association Reports, 1979-1989 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Support for Learning Subcommittees-Memos, Reports, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Technology Transfer- "The Agricultural Technology Delivery System", 1984 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Technology Transfer-Articles, Memos, Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Tropical Soils-Correspondence, Memos, 1982-1985 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Annual Report, 1955-1969 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, 1969- 1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mann Library Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Mann Library Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Mann Library Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - CUL Annual Statistical Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report (minus Public Services Report), 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Mann Library Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Provost's Report, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Annual Reports and Sarah Thomas Documents, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 32A)
  - Circulation Report, 1930-1945 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Statistics- Acquisitions, 1936-1956 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Statistics- Acquisitions, 1957-1963 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Statistics- SUNY Open Access, 1975-1982 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - History of Science, 1974-1979 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Committee on Academic Personnel Policy, May 9, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Library Proposal on Coursework, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - C.U. Libraries Admin. Council, 1960-1963 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - C.U.L. Communities, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - C.U. Libraries Cranch Report Rebuttal, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - C.U. Libraries-Development, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - C.U. Libraries Funds List, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Cornell University-Library Board, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Statistics- Loans, 1956-1972 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Review of Functions and Responsibilies, 1965-1980 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Records Conversion, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Information for Sarah Thomas for Provost's Report, August 1999 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Allocation and New Monies, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - 3-Year Plan, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Staff Numbers, 1952-1981 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Statistics- Loans, 1963-1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Statistics- Loans, 1963-1970 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Statistics- Loans, 1963-1970 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Statistics- Loans, 1930-1957 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Statistics- Loans, 1958-1963 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Statistics- Reference, 1951-1963 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Statistics- Coin-Op, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Annual Statistics, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Annual Statistics, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Annual Statistics, 1970-1991 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Annual Statistics, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Annual Statistics, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Annual Statistics, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Annual Statistics, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Annual Statistics, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Annual Statistics, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Annual Statistics, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Annual Statistics, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Annual Statistics, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Annual Statistics, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - CUL Annual Report Statistics, 1980-1981 to 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - CUL Annual Report Statistics, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - CUL Annual Report Statistics, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - CUL Annual Report Statistics, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - CUL Annual Statistics, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - CUL Annual Statistics, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Adminstrative Council Meeting-Minutes, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Adminstrative Council Meeting-Minutes, 1988-1991 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - CUL Automation Planning Project Phase II, July 1984- May 1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - CUL Automation Planning Project Phase II, July 1984- May 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Home Economics Library-Circulation Statistics, 1943-1952 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Home Economics Library-Circulation Statistics, 1943-1952 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Library Automation Planning Process-Schedules, Organization, and Deliverables, December 1983 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Mann Library Administrative Board, 1942-1954 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Mann Library Committee Minutes, 1950-1967 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Mann Library Council, 1976-1980 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Mann Library Council, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 11)